Finding Aid for the Norman Maurer Papers PASC.0086
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Artwork
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 6/15/1981 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    SCOOBY'S LUCK OF THE IRISH.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 5/18/1981 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    SCOOBY'S ROOTS.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO (Box 23, Folder 4)
    SCOOBY'S SWISS MISS.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 5/29/1980 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    SCOOBY'S THREE DINGALING CIRCUS.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 9/19/1980 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    SCOOBY'S TRIP TO OZ.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 7/22/1980 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    SCRAPPY'S BIRTHDAY.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO (Box 23, Folder 8)
    SIR SCOOBY AND THE BLACK KNIGHT.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 8/11/1980 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    SOGGY BOG SCOOBY.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO (Box 23, Folder 10)
    SOPWITH SCOOBY.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO (Box 23, Folder 11)
    SOUTH SEAS SCARE.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO (Box 35, Folder 27)
    STOW-AWAYS - REVISED VERSION.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 8/28/1980 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    STRONGMAN SCOOBY.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 5/27/1980 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    STUNTMAN SCOOBY - REVISED VERSION.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 10/14/1980 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    SURPRISED SPIES.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 6/27/1980 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    SWAMP WITCH.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 6/29/1981 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    SWEET DREAMS SCOOBY.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 8/29/1980 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    WAY OUT SCOOBY.
  - SPIDERMAN (Box 23, Folder 18)
    BUBBLE, BUBBLE, OIL AND TROUBLE - EPISODE #1.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 8/5/1981 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    ALIEN MUMMY - TWO COPIES, DIFFERENT DATES.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 8/19/1981 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    BAZAROWURLD.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 4/23/1980 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    BIGFOOT - FIRST DRAFT.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 8/7/1981 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    COLOSSUS.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 6/17/1981 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    CREATURE FROM THE DUMP.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 5/13/1981 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    ELEVATOR TO NOWHERE.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 6/23/1981 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    EVIL FROM KRYPTON (THE).
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 5/19/1980 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    ICE DEMON (THE).
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 6/30/1981 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    IRON CYCLOPS (THE).
  - SUPER FRIENDS (Box 24, Folder 6)
    KILLER MACHINES (THE).
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 6/30/1981 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    LAVA MAN (THE).
  - SUPER FRIENDS (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 5/14/1980 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    MAKE-UP MONSTER (THE) - TWO DRAFTS.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 6/5/1981 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    MXYZPTLK'S FLICK.
  - SUPER FRIENDS (Box 24, Folder 10)
    ONE SMALL STEP FOR MARS!.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 6/16/1981 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    OUTLAWS OF ORION.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 7/9/1981 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    PAULETTE'S PERILS.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 7/21/1981 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    SCORPIO.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 6/25/1981 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    SINK HOLE.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 8/17/1981 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    STOWAWAYS FROM SPACE.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 6/23/1981 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    THREE WISHES.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 7/24/1981 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    WARLORD'S AMULET (THE).
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 8/18/1981 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    WITCH'S ARCADE (THE).
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN (Box 25, Folder 1)
    ATTACK OF THE WARRIOR WOMEN.
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN (Box 25, Folder 2)
    BATTLE OF THE BARBARIANS - FINAL BOARD.
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN (Box 25, Folder 3)
    BROTHERHOOD OF THE NIGHT (THE) - ACT I.
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN (Box 25, Folder 4)
    CHALLENGE OF THE WIZARDS.
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN, 6/2/1981 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    CITY OF EVIL.
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN (Box 25, Folder 6)
    DEN OF THE SLEEPING DEMON - FINAL BOARD.
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN, 5/8/1981 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    FINAL BOARD.
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN, 7/13/1981 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    FORTRESS OF FEAR -TWO COPIES, ONE FINAL.
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN (Box 25, Folder 8)
    HARVEST OF DOOM -TWO COPIES, ONE FINAL.
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN, 5/15/1981 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    ISLAND OF THE BODYSNATCHERS.
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN, 8/11/1981 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    MASTER OF THE STOLEN SUNSWORD.
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN (Box 26, Folder 3)
    MINDOK THE MIND MASTER - FINAL BOARD.
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN (Box 26, Folder 4)
    PORTAL INTO TIME - FINAL BOARD.
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN, 7/31/1981 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    PROPHECY OF PERIL.
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN (Box 26, Folder 6)
    RAIDERS OF THE ABYSS.
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN, 3/24/1980 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    SECRET OF THE BLACK PEARL.
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN (Box 26, Folder 8)
    STALKER FROM THE STARS (THE) - ACTS I AND II.
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN, 6/20/1981 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    TREASURE OF THE MOKS.
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN, 7/15/1981 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    TRIAL BY TERROR!.
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN (Box 27, Folder 3)
    VALLEY OF THE MAN-APES.
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN (Box 27, Folder 1)
    WIZARD WAR!.
  - WILLIE AND LESTER (Box 27, Folder 7)
    'HAT' TIME IN WONDERLAND (A).
- Script material
  - ADVENTURES OF GOLDIE GOLD (THE), 7/22/1981 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    CURSE OF THE SNAKE PEOPLE - THIRD REVISION.
  - ADVENTURES OF GOLDIE GOLD (THE), 7/9/1981 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    GODDESS OF THE BLACK PEARLS - OUTLINE AND SCRIPT.
  - ADVENTURES OF GOLDIE GOLD (THE), 7/16/1981 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - ADVENTURES OF GOLDIE GOLD (THE), 5/26/1981 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    ISLAND OF TERRORS - REVISED COPY.
  - ADVENTURES OF GOLDIE GOLD (THE), 7/10/1981 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    MENACE OF THE MEDALLION.
  - ADVENTURES OF GOLDIE GOLD (THE), 4/10/1981 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    NIGHT OF THE CRYSTAL SKULL - PILOT (REVISED COPY).
  - ADVENTURES OF GOLDIE GOLD (THE), 6/29/1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    NIGHT OF THE WALKING DOOM - REVISED COPY.
  - ADVENTURES OF GOLDIE GOLD (THE), 8/10/1981 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    PERIL FROM THE PAST - FOURTH REVISION.
  - ADVENTURES OF GOLDIE GOLD (THE), 6/24/1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    PIRATE OF THE AIRWAYS! - REVISED COPY.
  - ADVENTURES OF GOLDIE GOLD (THE), 5/27/1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    PROPHET OF DOOM - REVISED COPY.
  - ADVENTURES OF GOLDIE GOLD (THE), 5/4/1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    RED DUST OF DOOM - REVISED COPY.
  - ADVENTURES OF GOLDIE GOLD (THE), 7/31/1981 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    RETURN OF THE MAN-BEAST - OUTLINE AND SCRIPT.
  - ADVENTURES OF GOLDIE GOLD (THE), 5/11/1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    REVENGE OF THE ANCIENT ASTRONAUT - REVISED COPY.
  - BENJI AS CAPTAIN CANINE SHOW, 12/18/1981 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    DEVELOPMENT FOR SATURDAY MORNING TELEVISION - OUTLINE.
  - CLUE CLUB (THE), 7/20/1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    ONE OF OUR ELEPHANTS IS MISSING - - TWO COPIES, ONE REWRITE.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS, 1/27/1980 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    AROUND THE WORLD IN EIGHTY VOLCANOES - PILOT SCRIPT AND OUTLINE.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS, 5/7/1980 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    BATTY BOO-TICIANS-TWO DIFFERENT COPIES.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS, 5/29/1980 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    BEACH BLANKET BOZOS - SECOND REVISION.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS, 4/14/1980 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    BUNGLING BABYSITTERS - FIRST REVISION.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS, 5/29/1980 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    CARNIVAL CUT-UPS - SECOND REVISION.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS, 4/14/1980 (Box 35, Folder 30)
    DETECTIVE DING-A-LINGS - FIRST REVISION.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS, 4/15/1980 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    DOOR TO DOOR SALESCREEPS - REVISED VERSION WITH NOTES.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS, 3/27/1980 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    HEALTH NUTS - FIFTH REVISED VERSION.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS, 5/28/1980 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    NO NEWS IS GHOUL NEWS - FIRST REVISION.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS, 11/7/1979 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    PREDEVELOPMENT - OUTLINE.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS, 4/9/1980 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    PREMISES.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS, 5/9/1980 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    PRIZED POOCH - TWO DIFFERENT COPIES.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS, 5/22/1980 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    RETAIL RUCKUS - SECOND REVISION.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS, 4/1/1980 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    SERVICE STATION SCREWBALL - REVISED VERSION.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS, 4/30/1980 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    SHOWBIZ SHENANIGANS.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS, 4/7/1980 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    TREASURE HAUNT - FIRST REVISED.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS, 5/22/1980 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    U.F.OAFS - TWO DIFFERENT COPIES.
  - DINGBAT AND THE CREEPS, 4/14/1980 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    WINDOW WASHOUTS - SECOND REVISION.
  - DYNOMUTT, DOG WONDER, 8/13/1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    AWFUL ORDEAL WITH THE HEAD OF STEEL (THE) - FINAL DRAFT.
  - DYNOMUTT, DOG WONDER, 8/26/1976 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    BLUE FALCON VERSUS THE RED VULTURE (THE) - FOUR COPIES.
  - DYNOMUTT, DOG WONDER, 5/26/1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    DAY AND NIGHT CRAWLER (THE) - REVISED FINAL COPY.
  - DYNOMUTT, DOG WONDER, 7/7/1976 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    DON'T BUG SUPERTHING - 3 VERSIONS WITH DIFFERENT DATES.
  - DYNOMUTT, DOG WONDER, 6/7/1976 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    EVERYBODY HYDE - SCOOBY CROSSOVER #1 FINAL.
  - DYNOMUTT, DOG WONDER, 5/7/1976 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    GREAT BRAIN...TRAIN ROBBERY (THE) - FINAL REVISED.
  - DYNOMUTT, DOG WONDER, 8/30/1976 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    INJUSTICE LEAGUE OF AMERICA (THE) - REVISED FINAL.
  - DYNOMUTT, DOG WONDER, 9/7/1976 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    LIGHTER THAN AIR RAID (THE) - FINAL DRAFT (3 ITEMS).
  - DYNOMUTT, DOG WONDER, 9/8/1976 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    PROPHET PROFITS (THE) - FINAL DRAFT.
  - DYNOMUTT, DOG WONDER, 6/25/1976 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    SINISTER, SYMPHONY -VARIOUS DATES.
  - DYNOMUTT, DOG WONDER, 8/9/1976 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    TIN KONG - REVISED FINAL.
  - DYNOMUTT, DOG WONDER, 1/16/1976 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    WHAT NOW LOWBROW? - FINAL DRAFT.
  - DYNOMUTT, DOG WONDER, 7/26/1976 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    WIZARD OF OOZE (THE) - REVISED FINAL.
  - FANGFACE, 6/23/1978 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    BEGONE, YOU AMAZON! - TWO DIFFERENT SCRPTS AND OUTLINE.
  - FANGFACE, 3/21/1978 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    CREEP FROM THE DEEP (A) - FIRST DRAFT.
  - FANGFACE, 5/15/1978 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    CUCKOO CARNIVAL CALAMITY (THE) -TWO DIFFERENT COPIES.
  - FANGFACE, 6/15/1978 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    DON'T ABBRA WHEN YOU CADABRA - SCRIPT AND OUTLINES.
  - FANGFACE, 8/8/1978 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    DON'T GET MEAN WITH THE COBRA QUEEN - NOTES APPENDED.
  - FANGFACE, 7/12/1978 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    GOOFY GARGOYLE GOOF-UP (THE) - TWO DIFFERENT COPIES.
  - FANGFACE, 3/29/1978 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    GREAT APE ESCAPE (THE) - FIRST DRAFT.
  - FANGFACE, 6/5/1978 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    INVISIBLE MENACE MIX-UP - REVISED VERSION.
  - FANGFACE, 5/5/1978 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    SHOCKING CREATURE FEATURE (THE) - TWO DIFFERENT SCRPTS AND OUTLINE.
  - FANGFACE, 6/12/1978 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    SPACE MONSTER MISHAP - THREE VERSIONS.
  - FANGFACE, 6/30/1978 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    TOOTHY SHARK IS NO LARK (A) - STEP OUTLINE.
  - FANGFACE, 7/31/1978 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    WHERE'S THE WOLF THAT'S THE WEREWOLF? - DIFFERENT COPIES.
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG, 8/4/1981 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    ALL THIS AND TIMBUKTU! - ACTS I AND II AND OUTLINE.
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG, 7/17/1981 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    AROUND THE WORLD IN EIGHTY WAYS - ACTS I AND II AND OUTLINE.
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG, 3/10/1980 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    CHARACTERS - FORMAT SUMMARY.
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG, 5/21/1981 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    DOUBLE JEOPARDY - EDITED VERSION.
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG, 6/11/1981 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    FJORDS AND SORCERY - TWO SCRIPTS, ONE REVISED.
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG, 3/26/1981 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    FRENCH CORRECTION (THE).
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG, 7/16/1981 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    GIVE ME A HAND--SOMETHING'S AFOOT - OUTLINE.
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG, 5/8/1981 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    IT'S ALL DOWNHILL FROM HERE - TWO DRAFTS.
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG, 4/16/1981 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    KELP!.
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG, 4/8/1980 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    KING FOR A DAY - OUTLINES.
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG, 3/14/1980 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    MACHO CAVEMAN (PILOT) -TWO DIFFERENT DRAFTS.
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG, 6/23/1981 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    PERILOUS PAULINE.
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG, 6/26/1981 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    THERE'S NO PLACE LIKE ROME - TWO SCRIPTS WITH DIFFERENT ACTS.
  - FONZ AND THE HAPPY DAYS GANG, 4/8/1981 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    TIME SCHLEP TWO SCRIPTS - WITH DIFFERENT DATES.
  - FUTUREMEN (THE), 11/6/1979 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    DEVELOPMENT - OUTLINE.
  - HEATHCLIFF, 11/2/1979 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    DEVELOPMENT FOR SATURDAY MORNING TELEVISION -REVISED OUTLINE.
  - HULK HOGAN'S ROCK 'N' WRESTLING, 7/24/1985 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    SPRINGBOARD PREMISE IDEAS.
  - INFERIOR FIVE (THE), 11/30/1979 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    MOST UNUSUAL DEVELOPMENT FOR TELEVISION - OUTLINE.
  - KWICKY KOALA, 11/14/1979 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    THREE PIGS II / HUNGRIEST WOLF / WOLF WHO CAME TO DINNER - OUTLINE.
  - LAVERNE AND SHIRLEY, 6/19/1981 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    APRIL FOOLS IN PARIS - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - LAVERNE AND SHIRLEY, 6/2/1981 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    BIGFOOT - OUTLINE AND ACT I.
  - LAVERNE AND SHIRLEY, 6/8/1981 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    HULA HORROR - PREMISE.
  - LAVERNE AND SHIRLEY, 7/14/1981 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    I ONLY HAVE ICE FOR YOU -TWO COPIES, ONE FINAL.
  - LAVERNE AND SHIRLEY, 4/15/1981 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    INVASION OF THE BOOBY HATCHERS (THE) - REVISED PILOT.
  - LAVERNE AND SHIRLEY, 6/1/1981 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    JUNGLE JUMPERS -TWO DIFFERENT COPIES.
  - LAVERNE AND SHIRLEY, 6/5/1981 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    NAVAL FLUFF; WITH OUTLINE.
  - LAVERNE AND SHIRLEY, 6/16/1981 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    NOT SO GREAT RACE (THE) - PREMISE.
  - LAVERNE AND SHIRLEY, 1/21/1981 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    SATURDAY MORNING SERIES DEVELOPMENT - PROPOSAL.
  - LAVERNE AND SHIRLEY, 8/14/1981 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    SUPER WACS - ACTS I AND II AND OUTLINE.
  - LAVERNE AND SHIRLEY, 8/11/1981 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    TOKYO--HO, HO - OUTLINE.
  - LAVERNE AND SHIRLEY, 8/12/1981 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    TWO MINI COOKS - ACTS I AND II INSERT.
  - LAVERNE AND SHIRLEY, 7/13/1981 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    WHEN THE MOON COMES OVER THE WEREWOLF! -TWO DIFFERENT COPIES.
  - MARMADUKE, 4/30/1981 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    GHOSTLY GOOF-UP (THE).
  - MISSION MORK (Box 31, Folder 3)
    CONCEPT FOR ANIMATED HALF-HOUR SERIES - OUTLINE.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 9/3/1982 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    ALOHA MORK -TWO DIFFERENT COPIES.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 6/21/1982 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    BEAUTY CONTEST (THE) - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 3/9/1982 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    BIBLE - SECOND REVISED VERSION.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 4/23/1982 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    BRAT (THE) - DIFFERENT VERSIONS OF PILOT.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 8/20/1982 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    COO COO CAVEMAN - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 8/9/1982 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    DISAPPEARANCE (THE) - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 6/17/1982 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    EVERY DOING HAS ITS DAY - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 9/3/1982 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    EXTRA TERRESTRIAL TODDLER - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 8/12/1982 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    FLUKE SPOOK (THE) - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 5/14/1982 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    GREATEST SHMO ON EARTH (THE) - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 5/24/1982 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    I CANNOT TELL A SPLINK - OUTLINE.
  - MORK AND MINDY (Box 31, Folder 36)
    IDEAS FOR STORIES.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 11/7/1980 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    INCREDIBLE MISADVENTURES OF SUPER MORK (THE) - OUTLINES WITH ANMATION.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 7/18/1982 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    INCREDIBLE SHRINKING MORK (THE) - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 9/10/1982 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    MONKEY ON MY BACKPACK - FIRST DRAFT.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 7/27/1982 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    MORK FOR MAYOR - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 8/1/1982 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    MORK FROM ORK - FIRST DRAFT.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 8/12/1982 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    MORK WITH THE MIDAS TOUCH (THE) - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 9/1/1982 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    MORK, P.I. - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 6/18/1982 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    MORKLE AND HYDE - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 6/8/1982 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    MORK-MAN vs. ORK-MAN - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 7/13/1982 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    ON YOUR MORK, GET SET, GO!.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 6/13/1982 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    ORKAN WITHOUT A CAUSE - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 4/23/1982 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    PREMISES AND NOTES.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 6/30/1982 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    RODEO RUBE - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 9/5/1982 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    SUPER MORK - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 9/1/1982 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    TIME SLIPPER SLIP UP - REVISED VERSION.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 5/26/1982 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    TO ORK OR NOT TO ORK, THAT IS THE QUESTION - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 7/8/1982 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    TOUCHDOWN MORK - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 9/10/1982 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    TREASURE AIN'T NO PLEASURE - - THIRD REVISION.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 5/27/1982 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    TRICK OR TRICK - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 7/7/1982 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    VISIT (THE) - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 7/2/1982 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    WHICH WITCH IS THE WITCH? - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - MORK AND MINDY, 8/9/1982 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    WIMP (THE) - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - MORK AND MINNIE, 1/2/1980 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    PREDEVELOPMENT FOR ABC SATURDAY MORNING TELEVISION - TWO COPIES.
  - MORK AND THE LAND OF ORK/MORK MADHOUSE, 8/25/1981 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    SATURDAY MORNING DEVELOPMENT FOR ABC ENTERTAINMENT - OUTLINE.
  - MORK IN THE MOVIES (Box 31, Folder 4)
    CONCEPT FOR ANIMATED SIX-MINUTE SERIES SYNOPSIS.
  - PITFALL HARRY, 4/20/1983 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    ALOHA HARRY - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - PITFALL HARRY, 4/4/1983 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    AMAZON JUNGLE BUNGLE - FIRST DRAFT.
  - PITFALL HARRY, 3/10/1983 (Box 31, Folder 37)
    DEVELOPMENT OF A SATURDAY MORNING SERIES - OUTLINE AND PRODUCTION SCHEDULE.
  - PITFALL HARRY, 4/30/1983 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    RAIDERS OF THE LOST SHARK - OUTLINE.
  - PITFALL HARRY, 5/3/1983 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    TIBETAN TREASURE TROUBLE -TWO DIFFERENT COPIES.
  - PLASTIC FAMILY, 4/16/1980 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    ABOMINABLE SNOW SPORT (THE) - FOURTH REVISION.
  - PLASTIC FAMILY, 5/22/1980 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    BABY PLAS' FINNY FRIEND - OUTLINE.
  - PLASTIC FAMILY, 4/1/1980 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    BAD LUCK STROLL - SECOND REVISION.
  - PLASTIC FAMILY, 4/7/1980 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    BASEBALL BULLY - FIRST REVISION.
  - PLASTIC FAMILY, 5/29/1980 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    CRIME COSTUME CAPER (THE) - THIRD REVISION.
  - PLASTIC FAMILY, 4/28/1980 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    HAIRCUT HEADACHE - SECOND REVISION.
  - PLASTIC FAMILY, 4/28/1980 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Q-BERT, 4/4/1983 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    DEVELOPMENT OF A SATURDAY MORNING SERIES - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - Q-BERT, 5/18/1983 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    DISC DERBY FIASCO - PILOT (4 ITEMS).
  - Q-BERT, 5/1/1983 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    GREAT Q-TEE CONTEST - OUTLINE.
  - Q-BERT (Box 36, Folder 19)
    RACE DAY RASCAL HASSLE - PILOT OUTLINE.
  - RICHIE RICH, 1/16/1980 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    ABC SATURDAY MORNING DEVELOPMENT - DIFFERENT COPIES.
  - RICHIE RICH, 6/30/1980 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    ABOMINABLE SNOW PLAN (THE) - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - RICHIE RICH, 6/8/1981 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - RICHIE RICH, 6/6/1980 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    BLUR (THE) - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - RICHIE RICH, 5/5/1981 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    BYE-BYE-BABY -TWO DIFFERENT COPIES.
  - RICHIE RICH, 6/1/1981 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - RICHIE RICH, 9/13/1980 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    CAVEBOY RICHIE - OUTLINES AND NOTES.
  - RICHIE RICH, 5/25/1981 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    CHILLY DOG - ONE "WORK COPY" OF TWO.
  - RICHIE RICH, 7/22/1980 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - RICHIE RICH, 6/22/1980 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    CONSTRUCTO - DIFFERENT COPIES.
  - RICHIE RICH, 6/17/1980 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    COUNTERFEIT DOLLAR - FIRST DRAFT.
  - RICHIE RICH, 7/29/1980 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    DISAPPEARING DIGNITARIES - SCRIPT AND OUTLINES.
  - RICHIE RICH, 7/23/1980 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    DISASTER MASTER - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - RICHIE RICH, 12/26/1979 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    DOLLAR'S THOUGHT BALLONS - ADDENDUM TO "BIBLE".
  - RICHIE RICH, 9/12/1980 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    GREAT CHARITY TRAIN ROBBERY (THE) - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - RICHIE RICH (Box 33, Folder 2)
    GREAT KANGAROO RUSE (THE) - OULINE WITH NOTES.
  - RICHIE RICH, 5/17/1981 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - RICHIE RICH, 5/7/1980 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    INVASION OF THE PLANET SNATCHERS - TWO COPIES, ONE ORIGINAL.
  - RICHIE RICH, 5/27/1980 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    IRONA vs. DEMONA - OUTLINE.
  - RICHIE RICH, 8/6/1980 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    IT'S NO GIGGLING MATTER - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - RICHIE RICH, 5/28/1980 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    KANGAROO HOP (THE) - THREE VERSIONS.
  - RICHIE RICH, 5/15/1981 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    KING BEE - REVISED SECOND DRAFT.
  - RICHIE RICH, 6/2/1981 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    MISCHIEF MOVIE -TWO DIFFERENT COPIES.
  - RICHIE RICH, 6/7/1980 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    MISS ROBOT AMERICA - SCRIPT.
  - RICHIE RICH, 9/1/1980 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    MOST UNFORGETTABLE BUTLER (THE) -TWO DIFFERENT COPIES.
  - RICHIE RICH, 6/16/1980 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    MYSTERY MOUNTAIN - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - RICHIE RICH, 2/5/1980 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    ONE OF OUR AIRCRAFT CARRIERS IS MISSING - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - RICHIE RICH, 9/5/1980 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    PHANTOM OF THE MOVIES - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - RICHIE RICH, 2/28/1980 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    PIGGY BANK PRANK - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - RICHIE RICH, 1/23/1979 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    PILOT - OUTLINE.
  - RICHIE RICH, 7/18/1980 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    POOR LITTLE RICHBILLIES.
  - RICHIE RICH, 9/4/1980 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    PRANKSTER BEWARE - SCRIPT AND OUTLINES.
  - RICHIE RICH, 4/8/1980 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    RARE SCARE (THE) -TWO DIFFERENT COPIES.
  - RICHIE RICH, 11/12/1979 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    RICHIE AND THE ROBOTNAPPERS -TWO DIFFERENT COPIES.
  - RICHIE RICH, 5/4/1981 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    RICHIE OF THE ROUND TABLE - REVISED SECOND DRAFT.
  - RICHIE RICH, 11/13/1979 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    RICHIE'S JUNGLE ADVENTURE - PILOT SCRIPT WITH NOTES.
  - RICHIE RICH, 6/26/1981 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - RICHIE RICH, 5/16/1980 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    ROBOT vs. ROBOT - HANDWRITTEN NOTES ON TITLE PAGE.
  - RICHIE RICH, 4/19/1981 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    SCHOOLHOUSE ROMP -TWO DIFFERENT COPIES.
  - RICHIE RICH (Box 32, Folder 8)
    SCRIPT BREAKDOWN.
  - RICHIE RICH, 5/21/1980 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    SHOCKING LADY STRIKES AGAIN (THE) - SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES.
  - RICHIE RICH, 9/19/1980 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    SINISTER SPORTS SPECTACULAR (THE) - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - RICHIE RICH, 5/29/1980 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    SNOWBOUNDERS (THE) - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - RICHIE RICH, 4/13/1981 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    SPACE SHARK - WORKING COPY.
  - RICHIE RICH, 4/17/1980 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    SPRING CLEANING - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - RICHIE RICH, 5/11/1981 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    VOODOO ISLAND - REVISED FIRST DRAFT.
  - RICHIE RICH, 6/28/1980 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    WELCOME UNCLE CAUTIOUS - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - RICHIE RICH, 5/15/1980 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    WHO'S AFRAID OF THE BIG BAD BUG - TWO COPIES, ONE WITH NOTES.
  - RICHIE RICH, 1/21/1980 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    WIPED OUT! - PILOT, ORIGINAL AND REVISED WITH NOTES.
  - RICHIE RICH, 3/26/1980 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    WOODLAND BLUNDERS -TWO DIFFERENT OUTLINES.
  - RUBIK (THE) AMAZING CUBE, 3/3/1983 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    BIBLE - FIFTH REVISION.
  - RUBIK (THE) AMAZING CUBE, 4/22/1983 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    PILOT.
  - RUBIK (THE) AMAZING CUBE, 6/20/1983 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    SPARKY AND THE POOCHNAPPERS - SCRIPT AND OUTLINES.
  - SABRINA'S MAGIC MADHOUSE (Box 33, Folder 22)
    OUTLINE.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 6/12/1981 (Box 5, Folder 7)